# JEFFERY KIMBROW

Email: kimbrowjeff@gmail.com Website: https://kimbrow-slice.github.io/JeffKimbrow/

Number: (913)282-2500 Location: Kansas City, MO

## **Skills Summary**

Experience using RESTful web services, creating Full Stack Applications using Node.js, Express.js, Mongoose and MongoDB. Experience with vanilla JavaScript, HTML5, CSS. Using JWT's for user authentication. Project management tools such as Git and GitHub. Experienced with creating projects in Visual Studio Code. Familiar with vulnerability testing in the HackTheBox.eu and PG Play Labs. Working on Kali Linux, Windows, and macOS operating systems.

#### Education

#### Software Development Certification February 2021

Currently enrolled in the *SkilledKC Technical Institute Software Development* program expected to graduate February 19<sup>th</sup>, 2021. As well as registered for the 90 days within the lab environment with the Offensive Security PWK OSCP exam.

#### **Experience**

#### Chipotle Mexican Grill LLC.

Take out Specialist | Chipotle Mexican Grill LLC. | 2015 –2016 |

Liaison between the customer and the front of the house. Cash handling, counting down the drawers as well as the safe at the end of the shift. Making sure that the customer satisfaction is met with orders being put on in a timely manner.

## Artist Helping the Homeless

House Manager | Artist Helping the Homeless | Oct 2020 - Present |

Manage and monitor overnight operations, Creating and filling out Excel spreadsheets, medication management, as well as case management, and statical collection of client demographics information.

## Volunteering

## Artist Helping the Homeless

Volunteer | Artist Helping the Homeless | April 2020 - October 2020 |

Community liaison between clients and staff. Supervising clients overnight, as well as populating excel spreadsheets.